

PROFILE

I'm Mehmet. As a Frontend Developer, I'm very passionate and talented about ReactJS, NodeJS, and MongoDB. I devoted myself to learn, implement, adapt and create through my life to build smart web apps to help people and improve life quality around the world. As a Junior Web Developer with 9 months of experience able to build web applications from the ground up-information gathering, planning, design, development, testing and delivery, and maintenance.

CONTACT

PHONE:

+306970438917

GitHub & Website:

https://github.com/sayinmehmet47 https://mehmet-sayin.vercel.app/

EMAIL:

sayinmehmet47@gmail.com

LINKEDIN

linkedin.com/in/sayinmehmet

CERTIFICATION

- FreeCodeCamp: JavaScript
 Algoritm and Data Structures
- FreeCodeCamp: Frontend
 Libraries
- FreeCodeCamp: Responsive
 Web Design

MEHMET SAYIN

Frontend Developer

EDUCATION

Turkish Military Academy - Ankara

2009 - 2013

Bachelor of Science: Industrial and Systems Engineering - 3.20/4.00

Social Hackers Academy - Athens

03/2021 - 10/2021

Learned Html, Sass, CSS, JS, ReactJS, Redux, NodeJS, TypeScript, Strapi. Firebase, Mongo DB, GitHub.

WORK EXPERIENCE

XYZ Reality - Frontend Developer

06/2021 - 09/2021

Building user interfaces for websites and/or web applications Working with ReactJS, Redux, TypeScript Creating self-contained, reusable, and testable modules and components

Writing some end-to-end test on Cypress, JestJS

Utest - Tester

03/2020-02/2021

As a tester, I tested various applications and websites, found and reported bugs. For example, I tested Letgo and Airbnb applications.

SKILLS

